在上集成长的烦恼中:
Previously on growing pains:
克莉丝:爸爸,我们浪费每秒钟都意味着糖果从我嘴边溜走.
Chrissy: Dad every second we waste is candy out of my mouth.
杰森:这样我想一直下雨的话,
Jason: So I thought with all the rain,
今晚一定可以是过以前朝圣者万圣节的美好夜晚.
tonight would be a great night to have the old pilgrim Halloween.
克莉丝:他们是怎么过的?
Chrissy: What did they do?
杰森:不是了,他们讲些恐怖故事.
Jason: No, they told scary stories.
开萝尔:如果是我初次约会的取消电话,告诉他我不在.
Carol: If that's my blind date calling to cancel, tell him I'm not here.
杰森:你好.
Jason: Hello.
开萝尔:告诉他我和非常帅气的人外出了.
Carol: Tell him I'm out with somebody incredible good looking.
杰森:那是埃迪的电话.迈克应该在半小时前去接他,
Jason: That was Eddie on the phone.
但是他没有出现.
Mike was supposed to pick him up a half hour ago and he hasn't shown.
克莉丝:雨足够小了.
Chrissy: It's light enough.
麦琪:关上门,克莉丝,你什么地方都不允许去.
Maggie: Close the door Chrissy, you're not going anywhere.
克莉丝:哦,不!真不出所料.
Chrissy: Oh no!It figures.
杰森:过来,关了灯,
Jason: Come on, close the light,
关上门,给我们讲些更加恐怖的故事.
close the door and tell us some more scary stories.
开萝尔:我脸上还没有化好妆呢.
Carol: I'm not finished with my face yet.
本:是呀,这样也许你只有到1992年的奥运会的时候才能准备好.
Ben: Yeah, well maybe you will have it ready for the Olympics of''92.
杰森:好了,谁愿意是下一个?开萝尔?
Jason: All right who wants the next turn?Carol?
开萝尔:哦,我不和你们一起,我只是在等那个僵硬的家伙.
Carol: Oh I'm not with you people, I'm just waiting for this stiff.
杰森:看来在这我可以请求一些帮助,本.
Jason: Looks like I could use some help here Ben.
本:开萝尔,现在就把你的屁股搬过来,讲个故事.
Ben: Carol, get your butt over here right now and tell a story.
开萝尔:不.
Carol: No.
杰森:本,我是说你说个故事.
Jason: Ben, I'm saying you say a story.
本:好吧,从前某个万圣节,在湿衬衫比赛上……
Ben: Ok, once upon a time on Halloween, at the sweat t-shirt contest...
麦琪:本……万圣节的故事,恐怖的.
Maggie: Ben...A Halloween story, scary.
本:好的,恐怖的.那是个万圣节,我放学回家.
Ben: Ok, scary.It was Halloween and I was coming home from school.
(开始描述故事)
(Story begins to be depicted)
本:妈妈,爸爸,
Ben: Mom, dad, it's your favorite son...you know...Ben....
你的爱子……你知道的……本……好了,我打算去我的房间学习了.
Ok well I'm going to be up I'm my room studying like Oas.
本:这很奇怪.
Ben: It was odd.
没人和我打招呼,没人弄我的头发,
No one to greet me, no one to tussle my hair,
然后我听到了一阵噪音……一种我从来没有听过的噪音.
And then I heard a noise...a stranger noise I had never heard before.
杰森:停下!
Jason: Hold it!
(故事结束)
(Story ends)
本:什么?我这次又怎么了?
Ben: What?What did I do this time?
麦琪:本,我需要一个恐怖故事,真正的恐怖.
Maggie: Ben I want a scary story, really scary.
本:好,好的,我这次明白你的意思了.
Ben: Ok, well, I got you this time.
克莉丝:我喜欢比萨饼的故事,本杰明.
Chrissy: I like the pizza story Benjamin.
本:谢谢你,克莉丝,
Ben: Thank you Chrissy, but this one is better.
但是这个更好.这个故事讲的是我为什么停止要糖果.
This is the story of why I stopped trick or treating.
(故事开始)
(Story begins)
对于万圣节,
I was like any other kid with this Halloween thing, you know...
我像其他孩子,你知道……有好孩子,
there were good ones, there were bad ones.
也有坏孩子.
I had been around the block a time or two...
我在街区转了一两次……我是说我一直去要糖果,从糖果是个忌讳词之前.
I mean I had been doing this trick or treating scam since before sugar
尽管这些年的要糖果,
was a dirty word.
有一家我从来没有去.
And through all those years of begging,
这事是公开的.别去布拉格家.
there was one house you never visited.
不是因为谁也没有看过他,
The word was out: Don't go to Bulager's house.
但是大家都听说过那些故事.如果你去那里,
Not that anybody had ever seen him, but we all heard the stories.
就回不来了.
If you went there, you didn't come back.
我意思是说,难道罗格一家就在那消失了?
I mean, isn't that where the Logger family disappeared?
他们十口人,消失的无影无踪.
All ten of them, wiped out without a trace.
我必须搞明白,
I had to find out, even if it was the last thing I ever did.
即便这是我做过的最后一件事.我不弄出声音.
I couldn't make any noise.
我可以跑,我可以慢慢的转动,
I could have run, I could have turned weenie,
但是我决定像个男人去面对这个.
but I decided to face this like a man.
奇怪的是,尽管我心跳的厉害.
It was odd, even with my heart beating like that.
一种奇怪的平静控制着我.我想这是因为那种气味.
A strange calmness took over me. I think it was because of that smell.
我是在哪里闻过那种味道的?
Where had I smelled that before? It was warm, inviting...
温暖,让人心动……带点奶酪味和带点牛至味.
with a hint of cheese, and just a dash of oregano.
(故事结束)
(Story finishes)
(啊---)
Ahhhhhhh...
(故事继续)
(Story continues)
本:等着,直到听完结尾,认真点.
Ben: Wait until you hear the ending, seriously.
杰森:开萝尔,你有什么能贡献的吗?
Jason: Carol, do you have anything to contribute?
开萝尔:我不想讲这些乏味的万圣节故事.
Carol: I don't want to tell these stupid Halloween stories.
麦琪:没有必要是万圣节故事,只要恐怖是恐怖故事.
Maggie: It doesn't have to be a Halloween story, just a scary story.
杰森:来吧,开萝尔,我有信心,你能使我们惊恐万分.
Jason: Come on Carol, I have every confidence you can frighten all of us.
开萝尔:那么,
Carol: Well, there is this dream I have been having...
那是我曾经的一个梦……我真的梦见过很多次.
I've been having it a lot actually.
(梦开始)
(Dream begins)
我在地铁站台,我迟到了.
I'm in a subway station, and I'm late.
在梦里讲话:每个人都去哪里了?今天是犹太人的某个节日吗?上我的火车……我跳过那个栅栏……不是那样做是错的,而且我从不做错事……这是我的悲剧.
Speaking in dream: Where is everybody?Is this some sort of Jewish holiday?Got to
make my train...I jumped the turn stile... no that would be wrong, and I
never do anything wrong...it's the tragedy of what I am
声音:请注意!别忧郁,
VOICE: Attention please!Stop winning and jump the turn stile.Yeah...
跳过栅栏.是的……我在跟你说话,书呆子.
I'm talking to you bookworm.
开萝尔:哇,你能相信我那样做了吗?
Carol: Wow, can you believe I did that?
奶奶:没关系,火车永远不会来了.
Grandma: It doesn't matter, that train is never coming.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
奶奶:我什么都没说.
Grandma: I didn't say anything.
开萝尔:哦,对不起.
Carol: Oh sorry.
奶奶:我是这样认为的.
Grandma: I thought it.
开萝尔:我能听见你的想法?
Carol: I can hear your thoughts?
奶奶:而且我也能听见你的.
Grandma: And I can hear yours.
开萝尔:我就准备不去理睬她,上火车,
Carol: I'm just going to ignore her, and get on that train,
离开这里.
and get out of here.
奶奶:火车不来了.这辆地铁叫成功.
Grandma: Its isn't coming, it's the subway car called success.
它不会来到那些只是等待它的人面前.
And it doesn't come to people who just wait for it.
开萝尔:那么,你在等什么?
Carol: Well, what are you waiting for?
奶奶:我一直在这等待.
Grandma: I always wait here.
自从我从上哥伦比亚大学一年级起就开始这样做了.我叫开萝尔 西维尔,
I have been doing it since I was a freshman at Columbia University.
你的名字呢?
My name is Carol seaver, what's yours?
开萝尔:你不是开萝尔 西维尔,我是开萝尔 西维尔.这太奇怪了.
Carol: You are not Carol Seaver, I'm Carol Seaver. This is so bizarre.
(音乐)
(MUSIC)
是的,开萝尔是奇怪,
Yes Carol Seaver is bizarre,
难道你不知道你就是那种类型的人.
don't you know that's the kind of person that you are.
别停下你所做的事;把它像罪过那样对待,
Don't let up what you did; treat it like a sin,
成为你那种类型的人….
to be the kind of person that you are...
想想你有知识,当你离开大学,
Thought you had the knowledge, when you went off to college,
你不再那里怎么办……
how come you not there anymore...
不适应,如此的不适应的人……或者我们可以叫你不适应的人?
Misses, such a miss-fit...or should we call you misfit?
你的整个生命被腐烂成石头……
Your entire life is rotten to the bone...
哈哈哈.
Hahaha
(歌曲结束)
(Song ends)
开萝尔:啊……(下落)
Carol: Ah... (falling)
我不相信,我在飞……我在飞.我不是一个紧张的怕疼的小书呆子.我可以做这个世界上没人可以做的事情.我是独特的.
I don't believe this, I'm flying....I'm flying. I'm not an uptight little bookworm who
is afraid to sore. I can do something that nobody in the entire world can
do. I'm special
迈克:嗨,哟,开萝尔!!开萝尔.
Mike: Hey, yo, Carol! Carol!
开萝尔:迈克?迈克.
Carol: Mike? Mike?
克莉丝:嗨,迈克,等我!
Chrissy: Hey Mike, wait for me!
本:嘟嘟,嘟嘟,成功.
Ben: Beep beep, coming through.
开萝尔:我不是独特的.
Carol: I'm not special.
克莉丝:嗨,你能从这看到我们家了.
Chrissy: Hey you can see our house from here.
本:是呀.
Ben: Yeah
开萝尔:啊……(落下)
Carol: Ah... (falling)
(梦结束)
(Dream ends)
开萝尔:什么?这里没有人有像这样的梦?
Carol: What nobody here has dreams like that?
每个人:哦,是的,对,是的……
Everybody: Oh yeah, sure, yeah....
麦琪:亲爱的,这只是一个梦,
Maggie: Honey, it's just a dream,
没有必要去担心或者为此害羞.
its nothing to worry about or be embarrassed about.
杰森:不,那是对的,
Jason: No that's true,
那明天我给你我几个同事的号码,
and tomorrow I'm going to give you some numbers of some colleagues of
你可以和他们谈谈,好吗?
mine you can talk to ok?
本:开萝尔,你的约会来了.
Ben: Carol, your date is here.
迈克:你好?
Mike: Hello?
迈克:迈克,是你吗?
Jason: Mike is that you?
迈克:是的.
Mike: yeah.
开萝尔:哦,太好了,只是我的傻哥哥.
Carol: Oh great, it's only my stupid brother.
麦琪:安静,开萝尔.迈克,你吓怀我们了,埃迪打电话过来了,你去哪里了?
Maggie: Quiet Carol.Mike, you scared the life out of us, Eddie called, where have you been?
杰森:出什么事了?
Jason: Something wrong?
迈克:是的,我说.
Mike: Yeah I'll say.
杰森和麦琪:迈克,怎么回事?发生什么事情了?
Jason and Maggie: Mike, well what's wrong?What happened?
本:迈克,你看起来见鬼了.
Ben: Mike, you look like you have seen a ghost.
迈克:哦,瞧,我没有疯,是吗?
Mike: Uh, look, I'm not crazy am i?
杰森:你在讲些什么呀?
Jason: What are you talking about?
迈克:我是说,我不是那种想象事情的孩子,是不是?
Mike: I mean, I'm not the kind of kid who imagines things, right?
麦琪:对的,亲爱的.
Maggie: NO honey.
迈克:这就是我所担心的.瞧,
Mike: That's what I was afraid of.
我根本就没打算今天晚上去埃迪家.
See, I never really made it to Eddie's tonight.
(故事开始)
(STORY BEGINS)
迈克:我想我知道长岛的每条道路.
Mike: I thought I knew every road in long island.
我会一切顺利的,没什么好可怕的……妈妈……妈妈……嘿,
I'm going to be fine, nothing to be scared of...Mommy...mommy...
你还好吗?
Hey are you ok?
卡拉:我想是这样..
Kara: I think so.
迈克:那好,那么发生什么了?
Mike: Ok, well what happened?
卡拉:我不知道……
Kara: I don't know...
迈克:没事,没事,没事……听着,恩,恩,你看到几根手指?
Mike: Ok, its ok, it's ok...Listen uh, uh, how many fingers do you see?
卡拉:两个.
Kara: Two.
迈克:很好,你想出去吗?
Mike: Great, you want to go out sometime?
卡拉:什么?
Kara: What?
迈克:哦,对不起,对不起,迈克 西维尔.
Mike: Uh I'm sorry, my name is Mike Seaver.
卡拉:卡拉 丹尼斯
Kara: Kara Danes.
迈克:好的,哦,你,你冰冷.
Mike: OK, Oh man you are ice cold.
卡拉:我已经在这一会了.
Kara: I have been here a while.
迈克:穿上我的夹克.
Mike: Here take my jacket.
卡拉:哦,谢谢你.
Kara: Oh thank you.
迈克:我很高兴你没事,瞧这车.
Mike: I'm just glad you are ok, look at this car.
卡拉:如果我擦弗兰克的车,他会对我发火的.
Kara: Frank is going to be so mad at me for toweling his car.
迈克:呀,你还活着,弗兰克应该高兴才是.
Mike: Yeah, well Frankie is just going to be happy that you are alive.
卡拉:你真有趣.
Kara: You are funny.
迈克:什么?
Mike: Pardon me?
卡拉:哦,弗兰克是极好的舞者.
Kara: Oh Frankie is such a wonderful dancer.
迈克:嗨,喔,喔.你确定你没事吗?
Mike: Hey wo, wo.Are you sure you are ok?
卡拉:哦,亲爱的,抱紧我,抱紧我.
Kara: Oh darling hold me just hold me.
迈克:好,当然,如果我开始.
Mike: Uh, well sure, if I got to.
卡拉:你愿意帮我?
Kara: Will you help me?
迈克:好啊,确切的说,那个弗兰克有多大?
Mike: Uh well, exactly how big is this Frankie guy?
卡拉:带我回去.
Kara: Take me home.
迈克:好的……哦,卡拉,你知道我们在哪里吗?
Mike: Sure...Uh Kara, do you have any idea where we are?
卡拉:知道.
Kara: Yes.
迈克:好的,你可以告诉我吗?
Mike: Well, would you like to share that information?
卡拉:为什么必须要结束这路程呢?
Kara: Why did it have to end this way?
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
卡拉:迈克,你曾经把某个人抱在怀里,
Kara: Mike have you ever held someone in your arms and felt eternal love
而且感觉到永恒的爱浸透你的灵魂吗?
wash over your soul?
迈克:数十次.
Mike: Dozens of times.
卡拉:你真可爱……哦,哇……
Kara: You are cute....oh, ohw...
迈克:你还好吗?我把车开路边去.瞧,对不起,这车的大部分是尖角和金属,让我瞧瞧.哦,唉,是个令人讨厌的伤口,我们得把它包好.如果它流血……卡拉,为什么它没有流血?
Mike: Are you ok? I will pull over. Look I'm sorry, most of this car
is just jag and metal. let me see that. Oh gosh that is one nasty
cut, we are going to have to get this wrapped. If it were bleeding....Kara
why isn't it bleeding
卡拉:伤口应该不是很深.
Kara: It must not be very deep.
迈克:你开什么玩笑?需要缝针.伤口消失了!
Mike: What are you kidding? This needs stitches. The cut is gone!
卡拉:我告诉你.
Kara: I told you.
迈克:好了,好了,让我瞧瞧另外一只手.
Mike: All right all right, let me see the other hand.
卡拉:嗨,瞧.这是我们的幸运地.
Kara: Hey look! It's our favorite place.
迈克:恩?
Mike: Uh?
卡拉:难道你记不得了?我们的第一次约会就在那.
Kara: Don't you remember? We had our first date there.
迈克:唉,卡拉,瞧,
Mike: Uh Kara, look, I have never been to this dinner in my entire life,
我在一生中从来没来参加这个晚餐,相信我,如果我和你曾经出去过,
and believe me, if I had ever one out with you I would remember.
我会记得.小男孩,我记得……
Boy, I'd remember.
卡拉:我跟你比,看谁先到门那.
Kara: I'll race you to the door.
迈克:好,她疯了,
Mike: Ok she's crazy, but she looks good. What am I talking about?
但是她很漂亮.我在说什么?这就是我所要等待的.
This is what I have been waiting for.
卡拉:雨停了.
Kara: It stopped raining.
迈克:这有匹马……哦,等一下,我忘了我的钥匙.
Mike: There's horses here...uh wait a second I forgot my keys.
卡拉:这!
Kara: Here!
迈克:哦,谢谢……
Mike: Oh thank you...
(进入)
(Enters)
迈克:哦,哇,
Mike: Oh wow, isn't Halloween great?
万圣节不好吗?我是说,每个人都参加化妆舞会.
I mean, everyone is having a costume party.
亚伯:等会,总统先生,我化装了.
Abe: Later Mr.President, I got a customer.
总统:别担心,亚伯;让他们自己找自己的房间.
President: Don't worry Abe; Let them find their own booth.
亚伯:房间,哪里?
Abe: Booth, where?
总统:哥达!!哈哈.
President: Gotha!!!haha.
卡拉:去我们常用的桌子.
Kara: Let's go to our usual table.
迈克:我们常用的桌子?
Mike: Our usual table?
小孩:我在8接球员游戏里打了50个本垒打.
Babe: I hit 50 homeruns in an 8 fielder game.
玛里琳:哦,算了吧,
Marilyn: Oh come on Babe,
小孩,美国佬的体育馆沿右线只是273.
Yankee stadium is only 273 down the right field line.
小孩:嘿,你懂棒球.
Babe: Hey you know baseball.
玛里琳:是的,我还懂胖子.
Marilyn: Yes, and I also know fat.
迈克:啊,哇,你就是活脱脱的玛丽莲梦露.
Mike: Uh wow, you are a dead ringer for Marilyn Monroe.
玛里琳:糖果.
Marilyn: Trick or treat.
卡拉:总统先生,他们占了我们的桌子.
Kara: Mr.President, they are at our table.
总统:嗨,你们俩,
President: hey you two,
你们占据这桌子已经有四个二十加上七年了.
you have been hogging that table for four score and seven years.
劳雷尔:算了,你们又把我弄进另外一个乱七八糟的事情了.
Laurel: Well there's another nice mess you got me into.
哈代:(无特色)
Hardy: (indistinctive)
山德斯上校:杜鲁门,你该看看我是怎么对付红豆的.
Colonel Sanders: And Truman, you ought to see what I can do with red bean.
杜鲁门:诺言,诺言.
Truman: Promises, promises.
迈克:唉,卡拉,瞧,我知道我不必告诉你这些,因为我知道你已经知道了,但是之前我从来没有跟你来过这.
Mike: Uh Kara, look, I know I don't need to tell you this because I
know that you already know,
but I have never actually been here with you before
卡拉:你说得对.
Kara: You are right.
迈克:哦,好了,卡拉,
Mike: Oh come on Kara don't cry...
别哭……我是说我曾经跟你来过这,很多次.嘿,
I meant that I have been here with you before, lots of times.
谁骗谁呀?我是常客!
Hey, who's kidding who? I am a regular!
嘿嘿,给我老样子,没有豆芽.
Hey hey, give me my usual, hold the sprouts.
卡拉:不,你只是一个多情的少年,
Kara: No, you are just a sweet dear boy who found a lonely soul on the
在路边遇到个试图找到归宿的寂寞灵魂.
side of the road trying to get home.
迈克:瞧,卡拉,
Mike: Look Kara, why don't you just give me your phone number and I will
你为什么就不告诉我你的电话号码,那样我可以给你父母打个电话,告诉他们你一切都好.
call your parents and tell them that you are fine.
卡拉:555-5406.
Kara: It's 555-5406
迈克:好,很好.你就坐在这,
Mike: Ok, fine.You just sit right here and relax, ok?
放松,好吗?一切都会好的.
Everything is going to be just fine.
卡拉:我知道,弗兰克.
Kara: I know it is, Frankie.
杜鲁门:他似乎是个不错的年轻人.
Truman: He seems like a nice young man.
卡拉:杜鲁门, 不错.我要给我鼻子搽点粉,我要回家了,杜鲁门.
Kara: Truman, be good.I'll go powder my nose, I'm going home Truman.
回家……
Home...
迈克:谢谢……对不起,你看见和我一起进来的那个女孩了吗?
Mike: Thanks...Excuse me but have you seen the girl I came in with?
亚伯:是的,谁---?
Abe: Yeah, whooooo
马克:不,不,不,我的意思是,她消失了.你说,我刚给她妈妈打电话,她在路边突然大哭,然后拖住我.她对你说什么了吗?
Mike: No,no,no, I mean she disappeared.See, I was on the phone with her mother, who by the way burst into tears and hung up on me.Does that say anything to you?
亚伯:什么是电话?
Abe: What's a phone?
卡拉:我准备好走了.
Kara: I'm ready to go.
迈克:哦,上帝!你怎么来的?
Mike: Good lord!How did you get here?
卡拉:你开车带我的
Kara: You drove me.
迈克:嘿,瞧,我刚才和你妈妈通电话,
Mike: Hey look, I was on the phone with your mother ok?
是吧?她开始哭,
She started crying and told me that I was playing some sort of cruel joke
告诉我说我对她开残忍的玩笑,然后她就挂了我的电话.你遇上什么麻烦了?
on her, and then she hung up on me.What kind of trouble are you in?
卡拉:过来,我告诉你原因.
Kara: Come, I'll show you the way.
迈克:去哪里?
Mike: To where?
卡拉:去那我十七年一直准备去的地方.
Kara: To where I have been trying to go for 17 years.
迈克:恩?
Mike: Uh?
男人:女士们,先生们,马上要上台的是我们的年轻人,我们从意大利来的小朋友,托普 斯哲.但是首先,
Man: ladies and gentlemen, now coming up soon for our youngsters up there,
正在台上表演的是,.吉米 亨德里克斯和李布那奇先生.吉米,李,请上台.
our little
friend from Italy, Topo Shizo But first, right here on this stage,
paradise dinner is
proud to present Mr.Jimmy Hendrix and Liberachi.Jimmy, Li, get up here
李布那奇:现在,吉米,现在是魔幻时间.
Liberachi: Now Jimmy, it's magic time.
亨德里克斯:是的,我和年轻的李.
Hendrix: Yeah, I'm with ya Li.
卡拉:走.
Kara: Let's go.
迈克:嘿,看起来好像你在漂向我.
Mike: Hey, it looked like you floated to me.
卡拉:我们马上到那里了.
Kara: We are almost there.
迈克:我没有看见房子啊.
Mike: I don't see any houses.
卡拉:迈克,停车
Kara: Mike, stop the car.
迈克:为什么?
Mike: Why?
卡拉:因为我到家了,我最终到家了.
Kara: Because I'm home, I'm finally home.
迈克:卡拉,我前不着村,后不着店.
Mike: Kara, we are in the middle of nowhere.
卡拉:和我跳舞吧,弗兰克.
Kara: Dance with me Frankie.
迈克:我是迈克,记得吗?
Mike: It's Mike, remember?
卡拉:请……
Kara: Please....
卡拉:嗯,卡拉,你现在迷恋上我了.
Mike: Uh Kara, you are loosing me here.
卡拉:就一会,
Kara: For one moment, that's all I ask.
这是我要求的全部.我知道我们发誓只爱对方,
I know we promised to love only each other,
但是我把你从那誓言中解脱出来.
but I release you from that promise.
迈克:谢谢.
Mike: Thanks.
卡拉:我希望你找到爱情,我希望你找到幸福.
Kara: I hope you find love, I hope you find happiness.
迈克:你知道的,卡拉,我只是真的希望你一切都好.
Mike: You know Kara; I just really hope that you are ok.
卡拉:我想你.
Kara: I miss you.
迈克:你这话什么意思?
Mike: What do you mean?
卡拉:我知道你会找到另外的爱情.
Kara: I know you will find another love.
迈克:瞧,卡拉,我有个主意.你说怎么样,我们回到车上,我开车带你回家,一切都会好的.好,来吧……显然你今天经历很多的打击,你还有点困惑.
Mike: Look, Kara, I got an idea. What do you say we get back in
the car, I'll drive you home and everything is going to be ok. All right
Come on...obviously you have been through a lot of shock today and you are
a little confused
卡拉:再见.
Kara: Goodbye.
迈克:嗨,等等,你去哪儿?
Mike: Hey wait, where are you going?
卡拉:回家.
Kara: Home.
迈克:回家?卡拉,瞧,那儿没有房子.
Mike: Home? Kara look, there are no houses up there.
行了,几英里内都没有房子……卡拉?卡拉?嗨,卡拉,
Come on, there are no houses for miles...Kara? Kara?
这不是开玩笑……卡拉?卡拉?你在哪儿?喂?
Hey Kara, this isn't funny...Kara? Kara? Where are you? Hello?
(故事结束)
(Story ends)
麦琪:亲爱的,你怎么样?
Maggie: Honey are you ok?
迈克:哈哈,你们知道,
Mike: Yeah, you know it's just that the one thing that makes no sense
这只是没有意义的一件事情,无论什么是……是……你们这些家伙怎么这么容易受骗.
whatsoever is...is...How you guys could be so gullible.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:什么也没有发生?
Jason: None of this happened?
麦琪:迈克,你吓死我们了.
Maggie: Mike you scared us to death.
迈克:因为这,这是个更好的晚上?
Mike: Is there a better night for it?
克莉丝:是啊,你制造了一个伟大的朝圣者.
Chrissy: Yeah, you would have made a great pilgrim.
杰森:你计划了一切.
Jason: You planned all this.
迈克:不,我没有,
Mike: No I didn't, I just planned to come home and scare Ben.
我只是计划回家吓唬本.我是说,我知道他会到这撒卫生纸.
I mean I knew he would be here toilet papering the house.
本:我已经这样做了.每个人因为这个责怪我,但是没有丝毫证据.
Ben: I have had it.Everybody is accusing me of this, but there is not
one scrap of evidence
麦琪:你的数百磅的两层卫生纸是怎么回事?
Maggie: How about your hundred pounds of 2-ply?
本:我回自己房间了.
Ben: I'll go to my room.
迈克:你们在这儿就是为了有个更好的万圣节.感谢这场暴风雨.
Mike: You guys being here only made it better.Thank goodness for this storm.
克莉丝:是,是,是.
Chrissy: Yeah yeah yeah.
麦琪:嗨,暴风雨,停了.
Maggie: Hey the storm, its over.
克莉丝:那么我可以出去了?
Chrissy: So I can go?
杰森:好吧,出去吧.
Jason: Yeah, go on.
克莉丝:走,走,走,走了,伙伴们.
Chrissy: Let's go let's go let's go, let's go maties.
麦琪:克莉丝,等我.
Maggie: Chrissy wait for me.
杰森:你不能再愚弄我第二次.
Jason: You didn't have me fooled for a second.
迈克:哦,拜托,
Mike: Oh come on dad,
爸爸,你怎么能穿条潮湿的短裤座在这儿跟我说那些?
how could you sit there in damp shorts and tell me that?
开萝尔:哦,不错,因此每个人都很高兴,除了好人老开萝尔.
Carol: Oh great, so everybody is happy now except good old Carol.
杰森:是.
Jason: Yep.
开萝尔:哦,那比小丑或者其他的要好……你好,
Carol: Oh that better be that clown or else...
我是开萝尔,卢-安的朋友……我哥,我爸……走吧.
Hello, I'm Carol, Lou-Ann's friend...this is my brother, my father...lets go.
杰森:我有没有和你说过,当我像你这么大的岁数,万圣节夜晚?
Jason: Did I ever tell you about the Halloween night I had when I was about your age?
迈克:说过,说过,说过,黄眼睛的故事?
Mike: Yeah yeah yeah, with the yellow eyes?
杰森:不,他们是桔色的眼睛.
Jason: No, they were orange eyes. But that's getting ahead of the story.
但是是那个故事之前的事情了.
It was a Halloween night, much like this...I was about your age..and...
一个万圣节的晚上,就像今天一样……当时我差不多你的岁数……而且……我没有糖果了……我给他们拿些水果.
I don't have any candy...I got to give them fruit.
迈克:哦,得了,爸爸,不要给他们水果.
Mike: Oh come on dad, don't give them fruit...
杰森:我们还有些什么?
Jason: What else do I have?
迈克:给他们一些钱啊.
Mike: Give them some money.
杰森:是呀,或者我可以给他们我其中一个肾.
Jason: Yeah, or I could give them one of my kidneys.
拉里:你好,我是拉里 莉奇,卢-安的朋友.我是来接……恩……开萝尔 洗维尔.
Larry: Hi, I'm Larry Leaky, Lou-Ann's friend.I m here to pick up..uhm
Carol Seaver
杰森:你和她约会的那位?
Jason: You are her date?
迈克:那么她和谁出去了?
Mike: Then who did she leave with?
开萝尔:我希望卢-安没有过分夸大我.
Carol: I hope Lou-Ann didn't exaggerate too much about me.
你是干什么工作的?
So what line of work are you in?
死人:采购.
Death: Procurement.
开萝尔:我们去哪?
每个人:成长的烦恼剧组祝您万圣节快乐!
00:22:28,100
Carol: Where are we going? Everyone: Happy Halloween from growing pains.